# **Kostiantyn Sharykin**

# Middle .NET Full-stack developer

Warsaw, Poland Remote work E-mail: konstantin.sharykin@outlook.com

LinkedIn: Link

GitHub: Link to profile

+48514115542

### **SUMMARY**

With over 3 years of commercial experience, I have strong hard skills, that will be required for creating high-quality, secure products. Also, I want to make an impact by programming, making life easier, teach people programming and I always strive to get new knowledge.

#### **HARD SKILLS**

**Back-end**: .NET, Entity Framework, ASP.NET Web API, ADO.NET, Dapper, NUnit.

Front-end: HTML, CSS, JS, Angular, Next.JS, Flutter, Blazor.

Databases: MS SQL, basic knowledge of NoSQL (MongoDB, Redis, Elasticsearch, Neo4j).

Others: Design Patterns, Refactoring, Git, Docker, Postman, Linux, Windows.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## December 2020 - Current | Full-Stack .NET Developer at Sysonline

EzPartsWeb.Mobile (Angular)

Developing and maintaining an adapted mobile version of Angular that supports custom SSO, forms, different views, browsing files, and complicated hierarchy.

### February 2019 - January 2020 | Right hand of the mentor at NovaLab

NovaLab was an experimental project of the Computing devices and programming department at National Technical University "Kharkiv Polytechnic Institute". The idea was to provide an alternative education. I completed tasks on time, reviewed and commented code of other people, and conducted workshops.

### June 2016 – September 2016 | Service wizard at Service center "Infinity"

Repaired software and hardware issues in laptops, tablets, and smartphones.

# **EDUCATION**

October 2022 - Current

Computer Science at PJAIT, master's degree

September 2018 - June 2022

Computer Engineering at NTU "KhPI", bachelor's

degree

#### **LANGUAGES**

English – Upper – Intermediate (C1)

**Polish** – Intermediate (B2)

**Ukrainian** – Native

Russian - Native